[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 5, "question": "Well, don't you think as a host, if I say this is what I want to talk about, that's what we should address?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "IN", "POS", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 6, "answer": "Not really, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 25, "question": "Are we done?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 26, "answer": "I'm not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 45, "question": "Well, don't you think as a host, if I say this is what I want to talk about, that's what we should address?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "IN", "POS", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 46, "answer": "Not really, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Christine O'Donnell"]}, "docId": "110819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RP", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "RBR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 51, "question": "Where are you going?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 52, "answer": "For one thing, after Christine O'Donnell walked off the set, she didn't have to talk much more about the campaign or the book.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 77, "question": "Am I guilty?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 78, "answer": "Piers, in this instance you are definitely not guilty.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 87, "question": "Did you think that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 88, "answer": "That was the impression I got as well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 95, "question": "Did you think I was crossing a line?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 96, "answer": "Speaking for all men, I absolve you from sexism on this as well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 108, "question": "What do you think, James?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 109, "answer": "I -- I think that's probably -- I think it's probably true, that if you're going out to promote a book you should be willing to talk about the book.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["James"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "RB", "RBR", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 127, "question": "What's your damning verdict?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 128, "answer": "Well, Piers, I do represent probably more sexual harassment victims than any other attorney in the country, and I will say this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 182, "question": "Christine O'Donnell, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 183, "answer": "I'm doing well.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Christine O'Donnell"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 200, "question": "You can be both, can't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 201, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 212, "question": "When you look back on it, what was the catalyst, do you think, or -- not your downfall but your hiccup?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "CC", ":", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 213, "answer": "Well, I think -- I like the way you say it's a hiccup.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 243, "question": "How can you be a witch?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 244, "answer": "Because I dabbled into witchcraft.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "Your first date was in the satanic altar?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":", "RB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 309, "question": "I would have thought there was a pretty good chance that you can make a pretty big move back into the political stage, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 310, "answer": "Well, I hope to stay in the political arena -- maybe not necessarily as a candidate or in an elected office.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 318, "question": "The problem, Christine, if I may just jump in there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 319, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Christine"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "RB", "RB", "VB", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "Do you still think masturbation is wrong?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "Let's not even go there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Catholic Church"]}, "docId": "110819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 376, "question": "So, am I right in assuming your views have evolved over the years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 377, "answer": "Well, I am a practicing Catholic and I support what the Catholic Church teaches.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "RB", "RB", "VB", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 398, "question": "Can I ask you, have you -- have you committed lust in your heart and therefore adultery?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 399, "answer": "Let's not even go there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 406, "question": "-- what is your view of gay marriage, for example?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 407, "answer": "I address that stuff in the book.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 421, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 422, "answer": "-- I obviously want to talk about the issues that I choose to talk about in the book.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 423, "question": "Do you answer that question in the book?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 424, "answer": "I talk about my religious beliefs, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 433, "question": "So, I'm bemused as to why you wouldn't just say it in an interview if it's in the book?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "TO", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 434, "answer": "Because I don't think it's relevant.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "You should restore that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "I'm not talking policies.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 447, "question": "Why are you being so weird about this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 448, "answer": "I'm not being weird about this, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 460, "question": "Well, don't you think as a host, if I say this is what I want to talk about, that's what we should address?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "IN", "POS", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 461, "answer": "Not really, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["6:00"]}, "docId": "110819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "POS", "NN", "IN", "CD", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "RB", "TO", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", ",", "RB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 468, "question": "You're leaving?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 469, "answer": "Well, I was supposed to be speaking at the Republican women's club at 6:00, and I chose to be a little late for that not to be -- you know, yes, not to endure rude talk show hosts, but to talk to you about my book and to talk about the issues that I address in my book.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 470, "question": "Have you read the book?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 471, "answer": "Yes, but these issues are in your book.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 477, "question": "Are we done?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 478, "answer": "He's still there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 493, "question": "But when you watched it, what did you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 494, "answer": "I mean, I thought it was odd that she walked off.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 518, "question": "What do you make of those two comments?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "That doesn't sound entirely consistent.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110819pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "CC", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 551, "question": "Do you have sympathy for him in the position he found himself in, where you have such an intransigent part of the Republican party really just refusing to compromise?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 552, "answer": "He appointed me and I stood up and took the appointment to serve my country.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]